

ABOUT

Date of Birth: February 27, 2001

Age: 20

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Location: Kwara State, Nigeria. Tel: +234 816 5602 856

Email: Shittut88@gmail.com

Portfolio: Acemetrixx.github.io

INTERESTS

Problem Solving

Books

Polishing Skillset

Mind Games

Physical Activities

Technologies

HOBBIES

Traveling

Gymming

Photography

SHITTU TUNDE

WEBSITE/GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a Certified Web/Graphic Designer with proven experience in creating elegant and inspiring designs for developing Companies and potential organizations. With 3 years of experience under my belt, I have strong hands-on experience across all graphic design areas. My skills include branding, print designs and web design. I communicate effectively, presenting my ideas in a way that is easily understood by users with varying level of technical knowledge. I have worked effectively both independently and as part of a team, and I am capable of being highly productive either way.

QUALIFICATIONS

2021 NATIONAL DIPLOMA

Degree In Computer Technology Federal Polytechnic, Offa.

2015 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Excellence in Graphic Design Course.
Guru Design Institute.

2019 FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Certification in Professional Web Design RisingStar Technologies.

2018 Marketing Expert

Excellence in PPC RNI Institute

2018 SSCE

Secondary School Certificate Mustapha Standard College.

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

2018 TO PRESENT | FIVERR

Freelance Website and Graphic Designer for various business and developing organizations. I create and develop website layouts, projects, business identity designs and other corporate brand designs.

Web Developer

2020 TO PRESENT | JWS CONSULT

Professional Website Developer for JWS Consult and other organizations. I create and develop website portfolios, Educational Platforms, Charity sites, Media Kits as a Junior Team Leader.

Computer Operator

2014 - 2018 | RANA COMPUTERS & PRINTS

Proficient Computer Operator at Rana Computers, a Senior Operator at Online Research, Data Entry, MS Word, Presentations, Excel, Coreldraw Expert, Mini Video Edit, Project Consultant, Typing and Research.

EXPERTISE

HTML & CSS

DREAMWEAVER

INDESIGN

ILLUSTRATOR

MS OFFICE

CORELDRAW

PHOTOSHOP

SKILLS

GOOD COMMUNICATION
TIME MANAGEMENT

TIME MAINAGEMENT

DIGITAL MARKETING

ADAPTIVE LEARNING CREATIVE SOLUTION

CLIENT MANAGEMENT

TEAMWORK & RESEARCH